SAM SKURIKHIN

E: sskurikhin3@gmail.com

P: +41 79 872 40 88

A: 7000, Chur Switzerland

SUMMARY

A bachelor graduate previously focused on working with web technologies and automated web testing. Knowledge and experience driven, dedicated to learn and adapt depending on the environment. Possessing a passion to continue the educational process based on the working cases. Flexible in terms of individual/team work, easy going, with sense of humor.

WORK HISTORY

Coinless.tips - Test Engineer

Remote, Switzerland • 02/2024 - 05/2024

Working in a Swiss Startup that provides the ability to transfer cashless tips for the Restaurants, Spas, Bars etc. Was mostly responsible for data transfer and backend testing.

- Executed a series of test cases to confirm system performance and reliability.
- Ensure backend systems meet performance, security, and reliability standards.

Meta - QA Test Analyst

Zurich, Switzerland • 08/2023 - 01/2024

Employed at META to work on cutting-edge VR technologies, specifically performing embedded testing for the META Quest product line, ensuring product quality and innovation.

- Completed the execution of regression test cases, validating system stability and functionality.
- Executed a series of test cases to confirm system performance and reliability.
- Investigated and reported software and hardware bugs, contributing to overall system quality.

Huawei Technologies Switzerland - Backend Test Engineer

Dubendorf(Zurich), Switzerland • 09/2022 - 02/2023

Worked on a high-profile project for Huawei in collaboration with Sunrise, Microsoft, and Nokia.

- Conducted comprehensive end-to-end testing and ETL testing, ensuring the accuracy of transmitted data.
- Maintained and managed testing environments to support seamless operations.
- Provided customer support for end-to-end test cases, enhancing client satisfaction
- Going through the logs ensuring the correctness of Data uploaded to the SQL Database

Tillo.App - Test Automation Engineer

Johannesburg, South Africa(Remote) • 02/2020 - 11/2021 Contributed to an innovative agricultural start-up developing a cross-platform application for data harvesting and visualization.

- Developed and prepared testing scripts using the Selenium framework with Python.
- Executed automated test scenarios to ensure the functionality.

SKILLS

Manual Testing, Automation Testing, E2E testing, Functional testing, Test Management tools, Quality Assurance, ETL testing

Python, HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, Flask, Javascript, React, Git, Docker,

REST/SOAP API, Postman, Oracle DB, Selenium, Firebase, SQLite

Linux, Bash scripts, Linux commands,

| EDUCATION

University of Plymouth

Plymouth, England • 02/2020

Bachelor of Science: Business Management

International University in Geneva

Geneva, Switzerland • 07/2018

Bachelor of Science: Computer Science

LANGUAGES

English

Bilingual or Proficient (C2)

French

Intermediate (B1)

German

Elementary (A2)

